const quizArr = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What is the Arabic name for Prophet Noah?",
    options: {
      A: "Nuh",
      B: "Musa",
      C: "Ibrahim",
      D: "Yusuf",
    },
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "What was the main message of Prophet Noah?",
    options: {
      A: "Worship many gods",
      B: "Worship Allah alone and abandon idolatry",
      C: "Seek wealth and prosperity",
      D: "Prepare for war",
    },
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "How long did Prophet Noah preach to his people?",
    options: {
      A: "10 years",
      B: "50 years",
      C: "950 years",
      D: "100 years",
    },
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "What did Allah command Noah to build?",
    options: {
      A: "A palace",
      B: "A temple",
      C: "An ark (ship)",
      D: "A city",
    },
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "What was the reason for the great flood during the time of Prophet Noah?",
    options: {
      A: "A natural disaster",
      B: "The people's disbelief and rejection of Noah's message",
      C: "A punishment for the animals",
      D: "A test for the believers",
    },
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Who were the only people saved from the flood with Noah?",
    options: {
      A: "His wife and children",
      B: "His followers",
      C: "His family and a few believers",
      D: "No one was saved",
    },
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "What did Noah send out to find land after the flood?",
    options: {
      A: "A dove",
      B: "A raven",
      C: "A falcon",
      D: "A sparrow",
    },
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "What is the significance of the story of Prophet Noah in Islam?",
    options: {
      A: "It teaches about the importance of wealth.",
      B: "It emphasizes the consequences of disbelief and the mercy of Allah.",
      C: "It focuses on military conquests.",
      D: "It highlights the importance of rituals.",
    },
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "What did the people of Noah do to him when he preached to them?",
    options: {
      A: "They accepted his message.",
      B: "They ignored him.",
      C: "They mocked and ridiculed him.",
      D: "They supported him.",
    },
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "What is the name of the surah in the Quran that is dedicated to Prophet Noah?",
    options: {
      A: "Surah Al-Baqarah",
      B: "Surah Nuh",
      C: "Surah Al-Anfal",
      D: "Surah Al-Ma'idah",
    },
    answer: "B",
  },
];

